<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CurveModifier on Curves Documentation</title>
    <link>http://example.com/curvemodifier/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CurveModifier on Curves Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:21:15 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.com/curvemodifier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Noise</title>
      <link>http://example.com/curvemodifier/noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/curvemodifier/noise/</guid>
      <description>The Noise modifier randomly modifies the output of the curve by adding simplex noise.
Types  Number List RGBColor HSVColor Vector3 Boolean  Constructor new Noise (  amplitude: number,  frequency: number,  seed: number = 0,  rangeStart: number | undefined = undefined,  rangeEnd: number | undefined = undefined, ) amplitude: The amplitude of the simplex noise.
frequency: The frequency of the simplex noise.
seed: The seed used to generate the simplex noise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clamp</title>
      <link>http://example.com/curvemodifier/clamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/curvemodifier/clamp/</guid>
      <description>The Clamp modifier clamps the evaluated value of the curve between a minimum and maximum value.
Types  Number List RGBColor HSVColor Vector3  Constructor new Clamp (  min:[Type],  max:[Type],  rangeStart: number | undefined = undefined,  rangeEnd: number | undefined = undefined, ) min: The minimum return value of the modifier.
max: The maximum return value of the modifier.
rangeStart: The time at which the modifier begins to modify the curve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sine</title>
      <link>http://example.com/curvemodifier/sine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/curvemodifier/sine/</guid>
      <description>The Sine modifier uses a sine wave to modify the output of the curve.
Types  Number List RGBColor HSVColor Vector3 Boolean  Constructor new Sine (  blendMode: SineModifierBlendMode,  amplitude: number,  wavelength: number,  phaseOffset: number,  rangeStart: number | undefined = undefined,  rangeEnd: number | undefined = undefined, ) blendMode: The manner in which the sine wave will modify the curve.
amplitude: The amplitude of the sine wave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step</title>
      <link>http://example.com/curvemodifier/step/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/curvemodifier/step/</guid>
      <description>The Step modifier transforms the curve into a step function.
Types  Number List RGBColor HSVColor Vector3  Constructor new Step (  stepLength: number,  rangeStart: number | undefined = undefined,  rangeEnd: number | undefined = undefined, ) stepLength: The vertical distance between each step.
rangeStart: The time at which the modifier begins to modify the curve.
rangeEnd: The time at which the modifier no longer modifies the curve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycles</title>
      <link>http://example.com/curvemodifier/cycles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/curvemodifier/cycles/</guid>
      <description>The Cycles modifier samples a defined portion of the curve and loops it throughout the modifier&amp;rsquo;s range.
Types  Any  Constructor new Cycles&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; (  startTime: number,  endTime: number,  rangeStart: number | undefined = undefined,  rangeEnd: number | undefined = undefined, ) startTime: The beginning time of the range from which the curve will be sampled for the loop.
endTime: The ending time of the range from which the curve will be sampled for the loop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>